The battle for all toy kind
Toy Story That Time Forgot is a animation, family,
adventure film directed by Steve Purcell.
During a post-Christmas play date, the gang find themselves in uncharted territory when the
coolest set of action figures ever turn out to be dangerously delusional.
It's all up to Trixie, the triceratops, if the gang hopes to return
to Bonnie's room in this Toy Story That Time Forgot.
Trixie (voice), played by Kristen Schaal.
Reptillus Maximus (voice), played by Kevin McKidd.
Woody (voice), played by Tom Hanks.
Buzz Lightyear (voice), played by Tim Allen.
Bonnie (voice), played by Emily Hahn.
The Cleric (voice), played by Steve Purcell.
Toy Story That Time Forgot, titled Toy Story: That Time Forgot on Disney+, is an American animated Christmas television special produced by
Pixar Animation Studios and Disney Television Animation and released by Walt Disney Pictures that aired on ABC on December 2, 2014.
Written and directed by Sam & Max creator Steve Purcell,
the special was produced by Galyn Susman.
Michael Giacchino composed the music for the special.
Most of the regular cast from the Toy Story series reprised their roles, including Tom Hanks as Woody, Tim
Allen as Buzz Lightyear, Kristen Schaal as Trixie, Wallace Shawn as Rex, Timothy Dalton as Mr.
Pricklepants, Don Rickles as Mr.
Potato Head, and Joan Cusack as Jessie, with Kevin McKidd and Emma Hudak joining
as new characters Reptillus Maximus and Angel Kitty, respectively.
This was Rickles' final TV special role before his death on April 6, 2017, and was the last Toy Story
production for four and a half years until the release of Toy Story 4 on June 21, 2019.
The special received critical acclaim.
The film explores themes of christmas, television special, short film.
The tone is lighthearted.